Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES II. CLASSIFIED FILES, 1921-80 (Part 1)
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES II. CLASSIFIED FILES (part 1)
  - Administration
    - Dr. Carrera, Michael A.
      - Sex Education Consultant, 1976-78 (Box 49, Folder 24)
      - Summary of Affiliate Sex Education Project, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 25)
      - Survey of Affiliate Sex Ed. Programs, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Staff
    - Elliott, Robin A.
      - Coordinator of Pop. Activities, Memos, General, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 27)
      - General Correspondence, 1970-71 (Box 49, Folder 28)
    - 1.61 Ewenstein, Edith
      - Correspondence, Memos
        - 1969-74 (Box 49, Folder 29)
        - 1975-78 (Box 49)
      - Family Planning Stamp, Guest List, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 30)
    - 1.61 Krosky, Robert
      - Krosky, Robert H., Correspondence, Memos, 1969-70 (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - Administration
    - Marshall, Tenny, Acting President, Correspondence, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 32)
    - Novick, Lee
      - Chronological file, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 33)
      - Coordinator Justice Campaign, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 34)
      - Memos to Affiliates, Regional Directors, Public Affairs Offices and Committees 1978 (Box 49, Folder 35)
  - Staff
    - Alfredo J. Perez
      - Correspondence, 1969-70 (Box 49, Folder 36)
      - Memos, 1969-70 (Box 49, Folder 37)
  - Administration
    - 1.61 Robbins, John C.
      - Abortion
        - 1970-73 (Box 49, Folder 38)
        - Loan Fund, 1973-74 (Box 49, Folder 39)
        - 1973-74 (Box 49, Folder 40)
        - 1975 (Box 49)
        - Congressman Hogan's Amendment and Discharge Petition, 1973-74 (Box 49, Folder 41)
        - Government Restrictions, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 42)
        - Loan Fund and Technical Assistance Program, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 43)
        - Loan Fund, Report and Proposal, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 44)
        - Public Affairs Funds, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 45)
        - Public Affairs and Public Affairs Strategies, 1973-74 (Box 49, Folder 46)
        - Proposal for Course of Action, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 47)
        - Strategy Session, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 48)
        - Technical Assistance, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 49)
      - Annual Meeting, Awards, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 50)
      - Staff 1970 Annual Meeting, Comments, 1970-71 (Box 49, Folder 51)
      - Board Resolution on Departure, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 52)
      - Changing Attitudes in the U.S. Towards Abortion and Voluntary Sterilization, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 53)
      - Comments on JCR "Newsletter," 1971 (Box 49, Folder 54)
      - Complaints About Service In and To the Affiliates, 1973-74 (Box 49, Folder 55)
      - Table of PPFA Payments to IPPF and Flow of Victor Bostrom Funds, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 56)
      - Staff, The Computer, 1969-71 (Box 49, Folder 57)
      - Correspondence
        - Miscellaneous, 1972-74 (Box 49, Folder 58)
        - 1971-74 (Box 49, Folder 59-60)
        - Management by Objectives, Five Year Plan, Correspondence
          - 1970-74 (Box 49, Folder 61)
          - 1975 (Box 49)
        - Staff, Correspondence, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 62)
      - Family Planning and Child Poverty, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 63)
      - Resources, Mary Faulkner, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 64)
      - Staff, Draft, City Council Resolution, Abortion, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 65)
      - Infant Mortality Rates, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 66)
      - Staff, Interviews
        - 1970-74 (Box 49, Folder 67)
        - 1975 (Box 49)
      - Resources, IT&T, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 68)
      - Invitations, 1970-74 (Box 49, Folder 69)
      - Job Description, Assistant to CEO for Affiliate, Center Coordinator, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 70)
      - Staff, Legal, Correspondence, 1970-74 (Box 49, Folder 71)
      - Letters of Commendation to PP-WP, 1971-73 (Box 49, Folder 72)
      - List of Individual and Organizational Memberships Paid for by PPWP, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 73)
      - Magazine Article by JCR, (Invitations, Projections)
        - 1974 (Box 49, Folder 74)
        - 1975 (Box 49)
      - Memos
        - Staff
          - 1970-71 (Box 49, Folder 75-76)
          - 1972-74 (Box 49, Folder 77)
          - 1975 (Box 49)
        - Committees Studying Aspects of the Organization and Resource Base of PPFA, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 78)
      - Morgan Guaranty Trust Company, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 79)
      - Move of the Federation Headquarters, 1974 (empty) (Box 49, Folder 80)
      - Newspapermen Seminar, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 81)
      - OEO: Proposed Study of OEO Supported Family Planning Projects, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 82)
      - Organization Relations
        - Name Change, Family Planning Clinics to Birth Control, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 83)
        - Staff, Participation in Academic Events: Lectures, Symposiums, Workshops, 1970-71 (Box 49, Folder 84)
        - Permission to Reprint, Permission to Translate, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 85)
        - Dr. Ronald Pion's Project, Sanitary Products, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 86)
        - Staff, Policy Making, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 87)
        - Population, General, 1970-74 (Box 49, Folder 88)
        - Staff, Population and Family Planning, A Review of the Literature, Correspondence, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 89)
      - Population Growth (Club of Rome), Correspondence, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 90)
      - Position Descriptions, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 91)
    - Public Affairs
      - Staff
        - Public Affairs Fund, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 92)
        - Public Affairs and Public Affairs Network
          - 1970-74 (Box 49, Folder 93)
          - 1975 (Box 49)
      - Relationship Between PPFA and IPPF, 1972-74 (Box 49, Folder 94)
      - Relationship Between CFPPD and PPFA, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 95)
      - Staff, Relationship of PPWP/PPFA/IPPF, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 96)
      - Report on the Federation, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 97)
      - Report to the Federation
        - 1975 (Box 50, Folder 1)
        - 1971-74 (Box 50, Folder 2-5)
        - Comments on "Report to the Federation," and Replies to Comments, 1971-73 (Box 50, Folder 6)
        - Draft of First Issue, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Robbins, John C.
      - Staff
        - Research Stimulation Project, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 8)
        - Resolutions and Controversies, 1970-73 (Box 50, Folder 9)
      - The Role of Doctors in PP Policy and Structural Changes, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 10)
      - Sex Education, Human Sexuality, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 11)
      - Staff, Speeches, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 12)
      - Statistical and Population Data, Fertility Rates
        - 1973-74 (Box 50, Folder 13)
        - 1975 (Box 50)
      - Sterilization, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 14)
      - Trip to Africa, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 15)
      - Trip to Turkey
        - 1972 (Box 50, Folder 16)
        - Report, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 17)
      - Wall Street Journal Column, Kristol, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 18)
      - U.S. Government Department of Health, Education and Welfare
        - 1973-74 (Box 50, Folder 19)
        - 1975 (Box 50)
      - U.S. Government National Center Health Services, 1973-74 (Box 50, Folder 20-21)
      - Yearly Growth of PP Affiliate Programs, 1970, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 22)
      - Staff, Voluntarism, 1970-71 (Box 50, Folder 23)
      - Women's Groups, 1973-74, [Chrons: Current Year (Except Confidential) See Chron. Files for Previous Years] (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Todd, Paul H.
      - Staff
        - Correspondence, 1969-70 (Box 50, Folder 25)
        - Memos, 1969-70 (Box 50, Folder 26)
      - Personnel, Correspondence, 1967-68 (Box 50, Folder 27)
      - Discussion Paper on "Causes," Policy, Program, and Allocation of Resources, 1968 (Box 50, Folder 28)
      - Western Region Director, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 29)
      - Staff, Organization, Relations, 1969-70 (Box 50, Folder 30)
    - Tsuruoka, Ted
      - Correspondence
        - 1971-74 (Box 50, Folder 31)
        - 1978 (Box 50, Folder 31)
      - Planning, Budget, and Internal Audit, All Staff Memos, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 32)
      - Survey of Public Information Budgets, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 33)
    - Vaughn, Jack H.
      - Chronological file, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 34)
      - Appointment as President, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 35)
      - (WR) Correspondence, 1975-77 (Box 50, Folder 36)
      - The National Liability Insurance Plan, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 37)
      - Invitations, 1975-77 (Box 50, Folder 38)
      - Memos, 1975-77 (Box 50, Folder 39-40)
      - Project Spruce-up, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 41)
      - Mr. Reckert's Report, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 42)
      - Publicity, Newspaper, 1975-76 (Box 50, Folder 43)
      - Radio and TV Appearances, Shows, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 44)
      - Resignation, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 45)
    - Klapper, Jerim, Field Staff, Correspondence and Memos, 1969-72 (Box 50, Folder 46-47)
  - Field Department
    - Rives, Sharon K.
      - Correspondence and Memos, 1970-74 (Box 50, Folder 48)
      - Affiliates Transferred from OEO to HEW, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 49)
      - How to Handle a Request on Starting an Affiliate, 1971-72 (Box 50, Folder 50)
      - Proposed Guidelines for Regional Office Monies, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 51)
      - Revision of "How to Organize a PP Affiliate," 1972-73 (Box 50, Folder 52)
      - Chronological file, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 53)
  - Veerhusen, Pamela
    - Assistant to the VP for Operations
      - Appointment, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 54)
      - Correspondence and Memos, 1979-80 (Box 50, Folder 55)
    - Director of Technical Assistant and Educational Services
      - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 56)
      - Memos, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 57)
    - TE and CS Department
      - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 58)
      - Board Effectiveness Workshops, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 59)
      - Seminars
        - Advanced Management Phase One, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 60)
        - Human Resources Management, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 61)
        - The Inner Game of Management, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 62)
        - Programming and Budgeting, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 63)
        - Seminar in Strategic Planning, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 64)
    - Director of Affiliate Services
      - 1971-74 (Box 50, Folder 65)
      - 1975 (Box 50)
    - Management Training Program Schedule, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 66)
    - Memos, Mimeos, 1971-72 (Box 50, Folder 67)
    - Newsletter, 1972-73 (Box 50, Folder 68)
    - Administration, Questionnaire to Evaluate Info on Oral Contraceptive, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 69)
    - TE and C Department
      - Training Programs Available Fall & Winter, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 70)
      - Training Program: Programming and Budgeting, Grant, Colorado, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 71)
    - Chronological file, 1972-74 (Box 50, Folder 72)
    - Chronological from October 1, 1974, Do Not Remove Contents 1974-76, [MISSING] (Box 50, Folder 73)
  - Administration
    - Wattleton, Faye
      - Appointment as President, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 74)
      - Correspondence, 1978-80 (Box 50, Folder 75)
      - Coordinated Mailing Program, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 76)
      - Performance Objectives for PPFA Board of Directors and President, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 77)
      - President and Board Evaluation Form, undated (Box 50, Folder 78)
      - General, 1979-81 (Box 50, Folder 79)
      - Memos, 1978-81 (Box 50, Folder 80-81)
      - Notes From the President, 1979-81 (Box 50, Folder 82)
      - Ohio House of Representatives Resolution no. 515 (on her appointment), 1978 (Box 50, Folder 83)
      - Publicity, 1978-80 (Box 50, Folder 84)
      - Remarks, Miscellaneous, 1978-80 (Box 50, Folder 85)
      - Speaking Engagements and Travel Schedule, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 86)
      - Chronological file, Do Not Remove Contents, 1978-79 (Box 50, Folder 87)
      - President's Bulletin, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 88)
    - Staff
      - Meetings
        - 1977-78 (Box 50, Folder 89)
        - 1968, 1970-73 (Box 50, Folder 90-91)
        - Minutes, 1977-78 (Box 50, Folder 92)
      - Seminars, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 93)
      - Orientation Seminar, Hotel Plaza, 1964 (Box 50, Folder 94)
      - Retreats
        - Tarrytown House, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 1)
        - January 1966 & April 1966 (Box 51, Folder 2)
        - 1965-68 (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - Studies
        - 1, 3/1953 - Revised, 1956 (Box 51, Folder 4)
        - 2, 1953 (Box 51, Folder 5)
        - 6, 1953-61 (Box 51, Folder 6)
        - Study Com., Non-Professional Workers, 1965 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - 1.61 General Services
    - Memos
      - 1971-74 (Box 51, Folder 8)
      - 1975-80 (Box 51)
      - 1970 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Handbook
      - 1973-74 (Box 51, Folder 10)
      - 1975-80 (Box 51)
    - Vargas, Robert J., Monthly Reports, 1970-71 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Operating Department, Leases, Correspondence, 1969-72 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Wats Line, 1972-73 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Robert Krosky's Memo on Duplicating, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Vargus, Robert, Staff, Correspondence and Memos, 1970-71 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - 1.61.2 Management by Objectives (Formerly PPBS)
    - A Survey of the Organization for Administration, 1966 [Copies 1 and 2] (Box 51, Folder 16-17)
    - Management by Objectives
      - An Affiliate Questionnaire on Five Year Programs, Activities and Priorities, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 18-19)
      - Federation Declaration of Principles and Purposes: A Family Planning Document, 1978-81 (Box 51, Folder 20)
      - Draft 3 Year Plan 1979-1981 and Comments, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 21)
      - Survey of Affiliates on 3 Year Objectives Programs and Priorities, 1979-81 (Box 51, Folder 22)
      - Five Year Plans
        - Report of Voting for 1974-78, January 7, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 23)
        - Introduction to the Plan 1974-78, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 24)
        - 1976-1978, Draft, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 25)
        - 1976-80, Revision, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 26)
        - 1976-80, Approved by the PPFA Membership, Oct. 22, 1975, Seattle, Washington, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 27)
      - Task Force on the Federation 3 Year Plan, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 28)
      - Draft of the Federation Three Year Plan, 1977-80 (Box 51, Folder 29)
      - The Federation 3 Year Plan, 1978-81 (Box 51, Folder 30)
      - A Five Year Plan: 1974-78, Approved by Membership, Oct. 1973 (Box 51, Folder 31)
      - The Amplified Five Year Plan: 1974-78, Drafts, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 32-33)
      - Basic Assumptions for Setting 5 Year Federation Objectives, 1975? (Box 51, Folder 34)
      - Five Year Plan, Draft Revision and Questionnaire for Affiliates, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 35)
      - Draft of the Revised Federation 5 Year Plan, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 36)
      - A 1972/1977 Five Year Plan, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 37)
      - Five Year Plan, 1970-71 (Box 51, Folder 38)
      - Five Year Plan, A Proposal for a 1971/1976 Plan for the PPFA, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 39)
      - Draft of One Year Plan, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 40)
      - Five Year Programs, 1961-66 (Box 51, Folder 41)
      - Outline of a Federation Three Year Plan, Draft, 1978-80 (Box 51, Folder 42)
      - Summary Tabulation to Affiliate Questionnaire on Five Year Programs, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 43)
      - Survey of Affiliates on Three Year Objectives, Programs and Priorities, Long Range Plan, 1978-81 (Box 51, Folder 44)
      - Five Year Plan, Voting Record Summary, Oct. 28, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 45)
    - Management Survey, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 46)
    - Management Studies, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 47)
    - Management Study, Cresap, McCormack and Paget, 1966-72 (Box 51, Folder 48)
    - Program Planning, Reporting System, 1971-72 (Box 51, Folder 49)
    - Program Planning and Budgeting System
      - 1968-70 (Box 51, Folder 50)
      - Proposal, 1969 (Box 51, Folder 51)
      - The Rand Corporation, 1965-70 (Box 51, Folder 52)
    - Implementation, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 53)
    - Program Responsibilities (Analysis), 1968 (Box 51, Folder 54)
    - Planning
      - Goals, 1965-67 (Box 51, Folder 55)
      - Internal, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 56)
  - 1.62 Alan Guttmacher Institute (Formerly CFPPD)
    - Abortion Survey, General, 1975-77 (Box 51, Folder 57)
    - Agreement, PPFA/AGI for Activities to be Performed for PPFA by AGI's Washington Office, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 58)
    - CFPPD, Analysis of Effect of Federal Funding on Affiliate Growth, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 59)
    - Annual Reports
      - 1968-74 (Box 51, Folder 60)
      - 1975-76 (Box 51)
    - Summer Apprenticeship Program for Medical Students
      - Guttmacher, Dr. A.F.
        - Staff
          - Invitations to Speak, 1969-70 (Box 52, Folder 1)
          - Invitations, Various, 1969-70 (Box 52, Folder 2)
          - Medical Literature to Dr. A.F.G. from A.P. Chakravorty, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 3)
          - Career and Employment Advice, 1969-70 (Box 52, Folder 4)
          - Criticism and Review Articles, Books, Films, and Manuscripts, 1969-70 (Box 52, Folder 5)
          - TV and Radio, Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 6)
      - Cuban Visit (Including Mexico City), l965-67 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Syllabus on Contraceptive Procedures, 1953-54 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - AMA, Twin Registry Meeting, 1956-67 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Conjoined Twin Symposium, Buford Nichols, Texas Children's Hospital, 1965-67 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Middle East, Correspondence, 1961-67 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Untitled, everything inside labeled, "CONFIDENTIAL," 1965-69 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Reports (Guttmacher): Cuba, Africa, AMA Infant Mortality Conference, 1966 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - National Association of Independent Schools, 1966-67 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Sanger Institute, Material on Both N.Y.U. and Columbia, 1963-69 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - AGI
      - Associates Letter, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - Board of Directors
        - Member List, 1977-79 (Box 53, Folder 2)
        - Minutes, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - Budget
        - Financial Status, 1977-79 (Box 53, Folder 4)
        - 1974 (Box 53, Folder 5)
        - 1975-76 (Box 53)
        - First Pass Budget from CY 1977, Approved by AGI National Council, 1976 (Box 53, Folder 6)
      - Bylaws, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - Bylaw Changes Relating to the CFPPD from AGI, 1974 (Box 53, Folder 8)
      - Certificate of Appointment of Board of Directors, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 9)
      - Certificate of Incorporation, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 10)
      - Data and Analysis for 1977, DHEW Five Year Plan for Family Planning Services, 1977-78 (Box 53, Folder 11)
      - Committees, 1977-80 (Box 53, Folder 12)
      - Dryfoos, Joy D., 1977 (Box 53, Folder 13)
      - Federation Coverage (Insurance) AGI, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 14)
      - Funding Proposal, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 15)
      - General Correspondence, 1977-79 (Box 53, Folder 16)
      - General
        - 1974 (Box 53, Folder 17)
        - 1975-78 (Box 53)
      - Grants, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 18)
      - History of AGI, CFPPD, Washington Office, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 19)
      - International Family Planning Digest, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 20)
      - Jaffe, Fred, Correspondence and Memos
        - 1974 (Box 53, Folder 21)
        - 1975-78 (Box 53)
      - Lease, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 22)
      - Kellogg Grant, Rural Family Planning Services Project, 1974 1974 (Box 53, Folder 23)
      - 1979 General Support Grant for and Washington Office Contract with AGI, 1977-78 (Box 53, Folder 24)
      - Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978 (Box 53, Folder 25)
      - A Policy-Oriented Research Agenda, 1976 (Box 53, Folder 26)
      - Position Paper on Public Policy and Legislative Issues in the Field of Fertility Control, Draft, (For Carter Administration), 1977 (Box 53, Folder 27)
      - Press Releases, 1977-80 (Box 53, Folder 28)
      - Procedures for Submitting PPFA's Comments, Proposed Federal Regulations, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 29)
      - Reorganization of PPFA Public Policy Activities, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 30)
      - Reproduction and Human Welfare: A Challenge to Research, Greep, Koblinsky, Jaffe, Sponsored by Ford Foundation, 1976 (Box 53, Folder 31)
      - Report on Promotion Program, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 32)
      - Resolutions, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 33)
      - Transition Arrangements, 1976 (Box 53, Folder 34)
      - AGI, PPFA/AGI Agreement and Deed and Copyright Document, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 35)
      - PPFA/AGI Negotiations
        - AGI Ad Interim Relationship Between PPFA, Inc & AGI, Harriet Pilpel, November 30, 1976 (Box 53, Folder 36)
        - Financial, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 37)
        - Ford Foundation, 1977-78 (Box 53, Folder 38)
        - Kellogg Foundations, 1977-78 (Box 53, Folder 39)
        - Novation Agreement US Government/PPFA/AGI, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 40)
        - Rockefeller Foundation, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 41)
        - AGI Proposed Agreement Between PPFA & AGI Drafts, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 42)
        - AGI PPWP/AGI Separation, Memos - Blaise, Vaughn, Pilpel, Tsuruoka 1976 (Box 53, Folder 43)
        - Transfer of Experience Rating Account Government of DC, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 44)
      - PPFA/AGI Special Affiliation Agreement
        - 1977 (Box 53, Folder 45)
        - Draft Comments, May 1977 (Box 53, Folder 46)
  - CFPPD
    - Annual Report, 1971-73 (Box 53, Folder 47)
    - The Cass Canfield Special Fund, 1974 (Box 53, Folder 48)
    - The Center's Future, A Report by the National Advisory Council, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 49)
    - Center's Impact on Family Planning Services to Patients, 1974 (Box 53, Folder 50)
    - Proposal for Extension of 5 Year Plan Contract, Region IV Plan, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 51)
    - Commonwealth Fund Grant for Family Planning & Abortion Studies, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 52)
    - Contract Between CFPPD & the Institute for Survey Research, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 53)
    - Center for Family Planning Development, General Correspondence, 1971-74 (Box 53, Folder 54)
    - National, 1968-70 (Box 53, Folder 55)
    - Comparison of 1968 & 1969 Surveys, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 56)
    - Cost & Funding, 1968-71 (Box 53, Folder 57)
    - County Study
      - 1970-72 (Box 53, Folder 58)
      - 1969, Correspondence, Memos, 1970-72 (Box 53, Folder 59)
    - Cumulative Report
      - 1966-71 (Box 53, Folder 60)
      - 1966-68, Technical Assistance Proposals, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 61)
    - Data & Analysis for 1974 Revision of 5 Year Plan for Family Planning, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 62)
    - Data & Analysis for 1973 Revision of DHEW Five Year Plan for Family Planning, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 63)
    - Expenditures & Funding, Temporary Folder, 1969-74 (Box 53, Folder 64)
    - Discussion of PPWP Technical Assistant Program, Paul Todd, May 12, Cleveland, May 30, Phoenix, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 65)
    - Draft of Possible Center Amendments & Board Resolution, 1974 (Box 53, Folder 66)
    - Estimated Fertility of Women by Status & Color, 1966-71 (Box 53, Folder 67)
    - Estimating the Need for Organized Family Planning Services, 1971 (Box 53, Folder 68)
    - Ethnic Composition & Location of Expanded Family Planning Services, 1970-71 (Box 53, Folder 69)
    - Family Planning Perspectives, 1969-74 (Box 53, Folder 70)
    - Family Planning Population Reporter
      - 1972-74 (Box 53, Folder 71)
      - 1975-80 (Box 53)
    - Family Planning Services in Region X, An Analysis of the Five Year Projection, 1971-75 (Box 53, Folder 72)
    - Federal Contracts & Grants, 1968, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 73)
    - Federal Funding & Its Effect on Affiliate Growth - Jaffe-Rosoff, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 74)
    - Federally Funded Family Planning Project Planning & Application Considerations Prepared for PP Affiliates & Agencies, undated (Box 53, Folder 75)
    - Financial Relationship CFPPD/PPWP 1971-72 (Box 53, Folder 76)
    - Financial Status, 1969-74 (Box 53, Folder 77)
    - Financing Birth Related Services in the US, A Fact Sheet, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 78)
    - Grants for the Support of the Center, 1971-72 (Box 53, Folder 79)
    - Highlights of the First Two Years, 1968-70 (Box 53, Folder 80)
    - Independent Evaluation of CFPPD & Its Future (Reports & Studies for Reference), 1973 (Box 53, Folder 81)